[
  {
    "question": "to come",
    "answer": "kommen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to be",
    "answer": "sein"
  },
  {
    "question": "to live/reside",
    "answer": "wohnen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to have",
    "answer": "haben"
  },
  {
    "question": "to be called",
    "answer": "heißen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to travel",
    "answer": "reisen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to run",
    "answer": "laufen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to play",
    "answer": "spielen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to celebrate",
    "answer": "feiern"
  },
  {
    "question": "to buy",
    "answer": "kaufen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to cook",
    "answer": "kochen"
  },
  {
    "question": "to drink",
    "answer": "trinken"
  },
  {
    "question": "Georgia",
    "answer": "Georgien"
  },
  {
    "question": "the siblings",
    "answer": "die Geschwister"
  },
  {
    "question": "the parents",
    "answer": "die Eltern"
  },
  {
    "question": "Turkey",
    "answer": "die Türkei"
  },
  {
    "question": "the student",
    "answer": "der Student"
  },
  {
    "question": "the dog",
    "answer": "der Hund"
  },
  {
    "question": "the German Shepherd",
    "answer": "der Schäferhund"
  },
  {
    "question": "on the weekend",
    "answer": "am Wochenende"
  },
  {
    "question": "in the summer",
    "answer": "im Sommer"
  },
  {
    "question": "the birthday",
    "answer": "der Geburtstag"
  },
  {
    "question": "the fruit",
    "answer": "das Obst"
  },
  {
    "question": "the vegetables",
    "answer": "das Gemüse"
  },
  {
    "question": "the food",
    "answer": "das Essen"
  },
  {
    "question": "on Sunday",
    "answer": "am Sonntag"
  },
  {
    "question": "the water",
    "answer": "das Wasser"
  },
  {
    "question": "the cup/mug",
    "answer": "die Tasse"
  },
  {
    "question": "the tea",
    "answer": "der Tee"
  },
  {
    "question": "old",
    "answer": "alt"
  },
  {
    "question": "single/unmarried",
    "answer": "ledig"
  },
  {
    "question": "much/a lot",
    "answer": "viel"
  },
  {
    "question": "big/large",
    "answer": "groß"
  },
  {
    "question": "black and blonde",
    "answer": "schwarz-blond"
  },
  {
    "question": "strong",
    "answer": "stark"
  }
]
